{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Window Replacement Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46355/":{"taskOID":46355,"originalTaskOID":46355,"setID":1150,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6829,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9732,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New Window(s) - Installation","answerDisplayText":"New Window(s) - Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9734,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair Window Glass","answerDisplayText":"Repair Window Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9733,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Storm Window(s) - Installation","answerDisplayText":"Storm Window(s) - Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9735,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair Window Frame","answerDisplayText":"Repair Window Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6830,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Windows","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many Windows are involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10707,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10271,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10831,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 5","answerDisplayText":"3 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10832,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 9","answerDisplayText":"6 - 9","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10833,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"10+","answerDisplayText":"10+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6829,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9732,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New Window(s) - Installation","answerDisplayText":"New Window(s) - Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9734,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair Window Glass","answerDisplayText":"Repair Window Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9733,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Storm Window(s) - Installation","answerDisplayText":"Storm Window(s) - Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9735,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair Window Frame","answerDisplayText":"Repair Window Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9732,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New Window(s) - Installation","answerDisplayText":"New Window(s) - Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9734,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair Window Glass","answerDisplayText":"Repair Window Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9733,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Storm Window(s) - Installation","answerDisplayText":"Storm Window(s) - Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9735,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair Window Frame","answerDisplayText":"Repair Window Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6830,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Windows","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many Windows are involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10707,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10271,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10831,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 5","answerDisplayText":"3 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10832,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 9","answerDisplayText":"6 - 9","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10833,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"10+","answerDisplayText":"10+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10707,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10271,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10831,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 5","answerDisplayText":"3 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10832,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 9","answerDisplayText":"6 - 9","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10833,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"10+","answerDisplayText":"10+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/46355/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46355,"taskName":"Windows - New","taskDescription":"New Windows","xmTaskDescriptor":"Window Replacement Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":280,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Glass Installer casement buy Frames","textMessagingName":"Inst Windows","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms replace existing windows or install new windows in structures. If replacing a window with one of a different size they will do the associated carpentry work, but may not be able to tackle associated brick, block or other masonry work. See separate category for firms that can handle associated masonry tasks. Also note there are separate categories for storm windows, sliding glass doors, doors, glass replacement \u0026 window mechanism repairs. When seals are gone \u0026 thermal windows become \"fogged,\" it may be possible to replace the thermal glass panes without replacing the entire window.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes thermal, greenhouse \u0026 bay windows.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Windows.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Window Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | New Window Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":22,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":46356,"bridgeTaskText":"Have broken glass in your window? ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"Replace window glass.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1897,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"New Windows","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"New Windows","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Window Project","urlName":"Windows-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Window Replacement Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install New Windows","searchKeywords":"Glass,Installer,casement,Frames,Multiple,Windows,installers,installations,thermal,efficient,energy,wood,Broken","emcCategoryOid":-12080,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1150,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}